<resources>
    <string name="app_name">List View Test</string>

    <string name="name">  This is a name </string>
    <string-array name="dist">

        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Barisal</item>
        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Rajshahi</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Barisal</item>
        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Rajshahi</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Barisal</item>
        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Rajshahi</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Barisal</item>
        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Rajshahi</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Khulna</item>
        <item>Barisal</item>
        <item>Noakhali</item>
        <item>Rajshahi</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
        <item>Dhaka</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="Dhaka">

        Dhaka (/ˈdɑːkə/ DAH-kə or /ˈdækə/ DAK-ə; Bengali: ঢাকা, pronounced [ɖʱaka]);
        formerly known as Dacca[13] is the capital and largest city of Bangladesh.
        It is one of the world\'s largest cities, with a population of 18.89 million
        people in the Greater Dhaka Area.[14][7][15] It is also the 4th most densely
        populated city in the world. Dhaka is the economic, political and cultural
        center of Bangladesh. It is one of the major cities of South Asia, the largest
        city in Eastern South Asia and among the Bay of Bengal countries; and one of the
        largest cities among OIC countries. As part of the Bengal plain, the city is bounded
        by the Buriganga River, Turag River, Dhaleshwari River and Shitalakshya River. The city is
        located in an eponymous district and division.

The area of Dhaka has been inhabited since the first millennium. The city rose to prominence in the 17th
        century as a provincial capital and commercial center of the Mughal Empire in South Asia. Dhaka was
        the capital of Mughal Bengal for 75 years. As the center of the muslin trade in Bengal, it was one of
        the most prosperous cities in the Indian subcontinent. The medieval city was named in honor of the Mughal
        emperor Jahangir and hosted the seat of the Mughal Subahdar (governor), Naib Nazims and Dewans (prime ministers).
        Medieval Dhaka's glory peaked in the 17th and 18th centuries, when it was home to merchants from across Eurasia.
        The Mughals decorated the city with well-laid out gardens, tombs, mosques, palaces and forts. The city was once
        called the Venice of the East.[16] Under the British Empire, the city saw the introduction of electricity, railways,
        cinemas, Western-style universities and colleges and a modern water supply. It became an important administrative and
        educational center in Eastern Bengal and Assam after 1905.[17] In 1947, after ending of British rule, it became the
        administrative capital of the East Pakistan. It was declared as the legislative capital of Pakistan in 1962. In 1971,
        it became the capital of an independent Bangladesh.
        Article 5 of the Constitution of Bangladesh declares Dhaka as the capital of the republic.[18]
    </string>

    <string name="Khulna">

        Processing.....
    </string>


</resources>
